There were
thousands of soldiers
Waiting for me to deliver
supplies and weapons.
You really think you're the guy
to step into this?
How badly does the director
want this war funded?
You do everything
like we said.
You walk in and out
like you own the place.
We can't just wait around
for him to kill us.
What you got in that bag?
Nothing.
Well. i guess you ain't
no one-hit wonder
After all. is you?
Take that
fucking backpack.
Yo. young blood. they fuck up
your shit already?
I saw you
talking to 'em.
You be really careful
about what you saying now.
Be real easy
to set me up.
You a smooth talker. but you
don't know shit about business.
You poach customers.
you gonna get blowback.
I imagine your connect ain't
gonna be too happy about that.
Question is. what you
willing to do about it?
who are they?
Now. why in the fuck
would i tell you that?
Because i'm asking.
Nicely.
I tell you who they are --
Next time i'm buying.
you be real nice to me.
You feel me?
Uh-huh.
Lenny and ray-ray.
They hooked up?
Western tribe.
Ask around.
You'll find 'em.
Happy hunting. baby.
I liked the other place better.
Me. too.
Oh. no. that's fine.
Yeah. just go right ahead.
These are decommissioned?
Well. no. i just lifted 'em
from the armory.
You think
anyone's gonna notice?
they're decommissioned.
They're on their way to
destruction at anniston.
How'd you...
I'm gonna redirect
a smaller shipment.
Call it an error.
and this batch is just gonna...
It seems like a lot of work
for some guns.
You didn't tell him?
You getting it now.
kemosabe?
No deal.
what?
I don't want any weapons that
could be linked back to the u.S.
You have any idea
what i went through
To get these fuckers loose?
I'm sorry that logan
wasted your time.
Oh. no. man. You're
wasting my fucking time.
Hey. give us a minute.
Okay?
A minute.
This was the only way
to get rocket launchers.
And when some new york times
reporter comes down there
To write about the conflict.
traces those serial numbers
Back to el toro.
and then to that fuck-wit.
Whose name do you think he's
gonna sing to get out of it?
No one's gonna check
the serial numbers.
I did.
Well. how are we gonna
fight the communists
If we don't have
any fucking weapons?
Okay.
You have a problem
with the serial numbers.
Yeah. and the crates.
Okay.
We'll repack them.
Once we get them
down there.
I'll have my guys
grind out the numbers.
Problem solved.
Okay. before we go. you and i.
we get power tools.
We grind the numbers out
ourselves.
Then we take them down.
Just us?
Do have any idea
how long that'll take?
Pedro.
does hector have kids?
Told you not to use
this shithole.
Fucking ants.
They're everywhere.
Can you focus
for once. please?
The only way to keep
your father's eyes off of us
Is to kill one of these five.
Make it look like they
took the money and ran.
So does hector have a family?
Yeah. but hector's
a bitch.
Father will be happy
to think he did it.
So he doesn't have kids?
No. he's got four of them.
They'll all be better off
without him.
Yo te dije no families.
Okay. then ron's out. too.
Tomás or enrique?
Tomás.
Why not enrique?
Because enrique
works security.
Just did six years
for manslaughter.
And tomás is a delivery boy.
That one.
Just tell us when it's done.
By myself?
Why not?
You already killed someone.
Reason we're in
this fucking spot.
I didn't have
a choice. ese.
You don't have one now.
Where my hot comb?
Lorraine. did you take my --
who took my hot comb?
Woodpeckers got
like extra-thick heads
For the pecking.
For real?
'sup. y'all?
Hey. franklin.
And that's why you
a peckerhead.
'sup. man?
You a peckerhead!
What's up?
Oh! Franklin!
How you doing. honey?
Hi. marla.
Oh!
Ooh. Oh.
Now. who dotted your eye?
Hope you ain't
out there scrapping.
No. ma'am.
Just caught an elbow
playing ball.
Oh. you lying.
You shut your mouth. boy.
Now. this one here
got his head on straight.
See. you might learn
a thing or two from him.
Yeah. a'ight.
hello.
Know about somebody lying.
don't you?
Just like your daddy.
You know about that. don't you?
Look like you been
up to some shit.
Where your toys?
Clean up this house!
I'm sick of this house
looking like this.
Hey. that never would've
happened you had me there.
Fuck.
Oh. sorry. man. My bad.
I was gonna hit you up
after a couple runs.
Once shit got real.
Guess shit
pretty real now. huh?
And you got to hand over
all that money?
Shit. i got you.
How you want to handle it?
Thought you might
know somebody.
Well. they ain't gonna
work for free. homie.
Yeah.
Vete a la gran puta!
It's gonna take forever.
My people are waiting.
We don't have time
for this shit.
The sooner we get
the numbers off...
...The sooner the i can
vet the customs guy.
Sooner we can go!
Hello.
Uh. speaking.
I'm s-- what? When?
Are...You sure?
In -- in l.A.?
Uh. no. no. no.
Um...I-i'll take care of it.
Thank you.
hey. i got to
take care of something.
I'll be right back.
You a'ight?
Yeah. just headache.
How much further?
Right here.
Beat that ass.
He's scared. look.
You can't work here.
bruh.
Hey. beat that bitch.
You trying to run?
Naw. bring that ass over here.
Get him. get him.
Kill him. j.J.
What i'm talkin' 'bout.
Hey. lookit. Look at them run.
look at them run.
You ain't going nowhere.
Fuck him up. j.J.
You know it.
I got it. i got it.
Ah. watch it. watch it.
Damn. man.
leon simmons. huh?
Lil leon.
I ain't seen you since wayside.
Kept in solitary for
scrapping with the cholos.
They was always
trying me.
Yeah. you try that shit
in tehachapi. nigga.
They'll eat your ass
for a snack. homie.
Fuck y'all want?
You want to make some ends?
Look. somethin' got took.
and we need to get it back.
What they take?
Doesn't matter.
Well. then roll up
out of here. nigga.
You up.
Hey.
Who it is done the taking?
Couple hustlers.
Lenny and ray-ray.
Lenny drive a cutlass.
Yeah. lenny and ray-ray.
Some old punk
motherfuckers. man.
Yep.
A'ight. Let's roll.
Uh-huh. there it is. see?
We was just hoping you could
tell us where they at.
Oh. yeah?
You take shotgun.
lil leon.
Leon's my name.
yeah. You got it.
leon.
Hey.
can you do that one?
Or this? Yes.
Can you put that?
Hey. Hi.
Look at this.
look at this.
Hi.
Wow. hi.
Oh. my god.
He got so big.
Yeah.
Hey. Wow.
Yeah. i know.
It's a good color.
Hey. buddy.
Um. i think that this one
Is supposed to be us.
yeah.
He's really talented.
How was the flight?
Ugh. long.
Did you give mom
a hard time?
No. he was great.
He stared out the window.
barely made a sound.
He slept.
Wow.
Mm-hmm.
You don't get that from me.
i know.
But i kept the barf bags
very close by just in case.
I --
Wow.
You look good. teddy.
I feel good.
I'm sorry. uh. you didn't
get my messages.
No. that's -- that's my fault.
I've been running around.
Yeah. the rest of my week
was sh-shaping up
To be kind of quiet.
Yeah.
It seemed like if we were
ever gonna do this. then i --
Jules. it's wonderful.
Mm.
I was trying to
get the a.C. Going.
Oh. yeah. it's kind of --
kind of been on the fritz.
But. uh. it cools off
at night.
Actually. there's
this. uh. this park.
This -- we should go.
Does -- does he like trains?
Of course.
You're not busy?
No. nothing
that can't wait.
I thought you said you were
running around crazy.
No. no. i didn't say "crazy."
But you're not doing
iranian traveler debriefs.
What did james tell you?
He said quite a lot without
actually saying anything.
You know...
I suppose that pretty much
says it all.
Uh-huh.
So...What's going on
out here. teddy?
they both live here?
Nah. just lenny
up in there.
How you know
he got the cash?
Oh. trust me --
lenny got your shit. homie.
'cause ray-ray's a bitch.
Hey. what's the plan?
A'ight.
What the fuck you doing?
Hey. lenny!
Open up the door. homie!
I got your little bitch
out here.
hey. lenny!
Man. what bitch
you talking --
uhh!
Get your ass down.
Close the door.
Grab that extension cord. homie.
Tie his ass up.
Fuckin' bitches.
Stop moving! Put your arm up.
Yeah. just like that. homie.
this little punk again. huh?
Ah. he's back for more.
Thought we fucked you up
before. huh?
Huh?
-Perfecto.
-¿sí?
-Delicioso.
Oh.
I smell bitches in here.
Sticky fiddling ass nigga.
Fuck wrong with you.
jheri-curl-looking motherfucker?
You htb?
Y'all to the curb asses
Need to the get
the fuck up out of here.
Where's my money. man?
Up your mama's pussy.
Hey. frank.
i can't find nothing.
'cause. dumbass. i don't keep
no fucking money here -- ever.
Oh. look! Fuck this shit!
Hey. you some stupid
Frankenstein humming
motherfucker.
Stop eating my shit.
What you say to me. homie?
You heard me. motherfucker.
Naw. i don't i can hear you
from way back there.
Come a little closer then.
Yeah? Say that shit again.
Fuck you --
Fuck me. huh?
Mm-hmm.
Keep talking.
Hey. look. Hey. now we both
can hum. homie.
Go say something.
Keep humming.
Mm-mm.
Mm. mm. mm.
Find anything?
Hey. now what it is
we looking for?
Hey. what we
talking 'bout. man?
Just a couple grand.
How much?
Couple grand.
His dumb ass keep his hoes
all over the place.
Them bitches steal
anything. nigga.
But you --
yeah. you all alone. homie.
You ain't got nobody. huh?
Where the fuck
them ends at. fool?
Hey. i got another song
you would like. though.
Whoa. hold up!
Let me holla at him
for a sec.
No. talk time is over.
Just bust his ass.
Can't tell us a damn thing
if he dead.
Goddamn. you soft
as baby shit. bro.
Hey. you hear that?
You got some ol'
Soft-serve ice cream ass niggas
with you. bro.
I don't see
no cupcake makers. man.
Hey. you don't like me
eating your food. huh?
Fuck your janky-ass food.
homie!
Nigga. fuck this shit!
nigga.
Fuck this shit!
It ain't got
to be like this.
Yeah. homie. Fuck all this shit!
Janky-ass place.
I'm gonna kill you. nigga.
i'll mess all the stuff
in here up!
You want to end up
dead. man? Huh?
Yeah. "f" me. huh?
Over what?
A few bills that
you jacked off of me?
I'll fuck
all this shit up!
just give it over.
Learn how to clean
your house. fool.
you see that man?
You next.
Where's my money?
yeah.
It's not that funny.
You don't even like
to take aspirin.
Okay. this doesn't require me
actually taking any cocaine.
I think he's
really enjoy this.
Yeah. he -- he likes
being in motion.
Teddy...
It's a rich
white man's drug.
You know? It's for
celebrities and spoiled kids.
Tell that to the coroners
in miami.
That's not gonna happen.
Not here. not if
i'm controlling who's buying
And who's selling.
you know?
This could turn
the entire tide of the war.
Okay. as a colleague. i can
kind of grasp that rationale.
But it's a little unnerving
that you won't at least
Acknowledge how...
Crazy this is.
Look. i get the faintest
whiff that something's off.
And i shut it down.
walk away.
This -- it -- it's not even
gonna come back to the agency.
It's not just the agency
i'm worried about.
Okay. it's not gonna
come back to me either.
It's not just you
i'm worried about.
Okay. let's just say
for a moment
That this is even possible.
Have you considered what
running something this dangerous
Will do to you?
Mentally.
Come on. that --
I'm fine.
I'm in a much better place now.
Yeah. because
you've been laying low.
But what happens when
this thing ramps up?
Which it will.
You don't remember tehran?
Why do you have to put
yourself in this position?
Because it's important.
'cause the country's
asking me to do it.
I...I mean. i thought that's
what we were doing here.
Yeah. i guess it is.
Go. Go make your call.
It's fine. really.
Go.
Uh...
It'll just take a second.
Mm-hmm.
He really is
getting so big.
Hello.
Hey. how's it going?
It's gonna take me days if
i have to do all these myself.
Where the hell are you?
Listen. i just need
a little more time.
How much?
I'm not sure. but. uh.
i'm gonna try to get back soon.
Anything else?
Uh. no.
Great.
You're doing so good.
Hmm?
Y'all been here
all day. man.
Hey.
You ain't find nothin'?
I promise you
it's not up there. homie.
Man. i told you.
He wasn't gonna
give up on nothin'.
Wake up. homie.
Franklin.
My money's
got to be here.
Lenny.
shh. shh.
Come on.
let's get it. bro.
we're going to fox hills mall
and pick up some staceys.
Come on. bruh.
they gon' sell out.
You in there? Let's go!
Lenny!
This a bitch.
I'm out.
No time for this shit. man.
Move.
Hey. you don't like
my humming. huh?
Hold up.
Get out my face.
fuck you like
my humming now?
breathe. nigga.
Stand up. nigga.
Ohh!
Where my money at.
homie?!
Where the fuck
is my money?
Fuck you!
Oh. god!
Shit!
The fuck you doing?
Shut the fuck up.
Fuck off of me!
Shut your ass up!
Get the fuck off of me!
Fuck up. nigga.
Nigga. get off! Aah!
You don't know where
the money at. huh?
This is fucked.
You're kidding me.
He's a pinche maricón?
So. is it done?
No.
Why not?
Didn't want to.
You couldn't take them?
You could have waited
till he was alone.
Dije no families.
He's a pinche maricón.
You should have just
taken both of them.
It wasn't right.
carajo.
Or maybe i should
just go to my father.
Tell him you killed max.
Okay.
You want me dead?
do it right now.
Yeah. you don't
think i'll do it?
-Ándele.
You don't think i'll do it?
Stop it!
Should be enrique.
No. i told you
enrique's a killer.
I'll do it. lucia.
Pero you're both
going to be there.
Watch it happen.
Cuando estás listo.
Get off me!
Fuck your shit!
Shut your ass up.
Get the fuck off me.
Shut your ass up. nigga.
Yeah. talk shit now.
The fuck you doing?
Shut your ass up.
The fuck. man?
Uh-huh.
What are you doing?
Get your ass down. yeah.
What now?
Where the money at. homie?
Where that money at?
He's killing him. man.
Talk shit now.
Say something.
Get off me. man.
Fuck me. huh?
say something now.
Shit.
What?
He ain't killing him.
He -- he giving it to him.
Say something.
Not what
you were hoping for?
Is he out?
No.
I don't know.
It's been
a huge day for him.
He'll be okay.
You should go. teddy.
No. that's okay.
Uh. hey. you hungry?
There's this
great mexican place.
No.
I'm telling you
you should go.
Go do what it is
that you need to do.
Um. let us
stay the night here.
And then we'll be gone
in the morning.
Wait. what?
Uh. what?
You don't
have to do this.
Do what?
This.
This thing that we do.
where you tell me
What you think i want to hear
instead of telling me the truth.
Okay.
Uh. what's the truth?
That we were stationed
together. and it was...
It was fucking great.
It was romantic and exotic.
and i got pregnant.
And instead of telling me
you weren't ready.
You told me you loved me.
Bec-- i do.
I love you.
I love both of you.
I know.
And i know that being sent
to l.A. Wasn't your choice.
Yeah. that's right.
It wasn't my...Choice.
But now you're making
a choice to dig in here
And be a part of something
that i can't support.
Okay. look.
I think that you're making
Way more of this than it --
it's gonna be.
Teddy. i think you are
making way too little of it.
Look.
I have money.
I have
plenty of support.
We'll be fine.
We are fine.
We're fine.
If this is what you need to do.
if this is what
You think the country needs
you to do. teddy. then do it.
Please. come on. let's...
...Talk about this
when i get back to d.C.
You want to come back
to d.C.?
Come on.
You know where we are.
It's not
a bad thing. teddy.
Hey. buddy.
I love you.
now go to sleep.
Yeah.
Okay.
Can i keep this?
Go to sleep.
Couple grand. huh?
Karvel. hold up.
That's my money.
Órale.
know what? Maybe you can
Stay in the stash house.
watch over everything.
Long as you don't
mind the ants.
Why wrestling?
Can't be the money.
I just like it.
Those luchadores
were my heroes growing up.
What did you think
it was going to be?
Fame?
ladies.
I thought it would
make me feel...
Good.
And it doesn't?
Un carro.
pedro.
What the fuck?
Shh. Look.
He's big. that vato.
Told you he's security.
Okay. look.
I'll go to the door.
He'll let me in. I'll make sure
the door's unlocked.
You two go in behind me.
Órale.
Dale.
Just wait
till i'm inside.
Mnh-mnh.
So. run it down.
What happened?
Nothin' that
can't be handled.
Y'all gonna save me some?
Claudia?
Nah. Somethin' else.
What you need?
I need a gun.
Stop.
You sure about that?
I ain't your
fucking mama. man.
You take that gun
out of this house.
You better
be ready to use it.
You pull it. you hesitate.
that's your funeral.
And if you
make that mistake
And your mama show up here.
Wilin' out of her mind...
You can be sure
She'll know that i wasn't the
one that gave you that piece.
Ah!
You see. son...
Hey. Where have
you been all day?
Cho's.
Hmm?
Oh. it's fine.
Some shelves fell on me.
Oh. my god. Let me see.
It's fine.
Just kind of sore.
Well. then you should think
about getting a different job.
Yeah.
Thinking about that.
You sure you're okay?
Just tired.
It just might work.
This is the good part.
Jumped off the balcony.
What'chu talkin' about. dad?
I love this.